<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>Atlantic Fleet</title>
    <link href="https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet" />
    <updated>2024-07-03T00:07:00-07:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>warelock</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Fleet Google Calendar</title>
        <author>
            <name>warelock</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet/fleet-google-calendar.html"/>
        <id>https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet/fleet-google-calendar.html</id>

        <updated>2024-07-02T21:33:59-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We recently added a public Atlantic R&amp;D Fleet Google Calendar that mirrors all Discord events we schedule. Follow this procedure to add our calendar and never miss another developer voice call/meeting again: In your web browser: Add the Pirate Chain Atlantic R&amp;D Fleet Discord Scheduled&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We recently added a public Atlantic R&amp;D Fleet Google Calendar that mirrors all Discord events we schedule. Follow this procedure to add our calendar and never miss another developer voice call/meeting again:</p>
<ol start="1">
<li>In your web browser: Add the Pirate Chain Atlantic R&amp;D Fleet Discord Scheduled Events Google Calendar <a href="https://301.link/atlanticfleet" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</li>
<li>In Google Calendar: Look on the left side of the Google Calendar window for the Atlantic Fleet calendar you just added</li>
<li>Hover your mouse over the calendar entry, see the calendar's triple-dot menu, and click it</li>
<li>Settings &gt; Event Notifications &gt; Add notification &gt; Set the default reminder for all Atlantic Fleet events to whatever you want (I suggest 15 minutes)</li>
</ol>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <author>
            <name>warelock</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet/welcome.html"/>
        <id>https://atlanticfleet.github.io/atlanticFleet/welcome.html</id>

        <updated>2024-07-02T21:25:23-07:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                    We are a group of enthusiasts and activists who have come together to actively contribute to the Pirate Chain cryptocurrency privacy and anonymity project. We have a dedicated Discord server and Github organization. In our Discord developer calls, we discuss ongoing projects, brainstorm new project&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                <p>We are a group of enthusiasts and activists who have come together to actively contribute to the Pirate Chain cryptocurrency privacy and anonymity project.</p>
<p>We have a dedicated Discord server and Github organization. In our Discord developer calls, we discuss ongoing projects, brainstorm new project ideas, and mutually, generally support each other as enthusiasts and contributors to the Pirate Chain cryptocurrency privacy and anonymity project.</p>
<p>The Pirate Chain project's future success depends on * your * participation. The Atlantic R&amp;D Fleet is looking for people with skills in any or all of the following areas:</p>
<ul>
<li>Software Development
<ul>
<li>C++/Qt5</li>
<li>Python3/PyQt5</li>
<li>Cryptography, applied to Cryptocurrencies</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Project Management</li>
<li>Technical Documentation</li>
<li>Business/E-Commerce</li>
</ul>
<p>Even if you are just very technically minded and think you have great ideas about where you think Pirate Chain can be improved, your participation is eagerly welcomed. Please join the Pirate Chain Discord server and reach out to warelock (@warelock) and/or Øswald (@piratechain) for further details.</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
